{
    "subject": "resource/Statistical_finance",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Mathematical_finance",
    "human_readable": "Statistical finance is about Mathematical finance.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9293627142906189,
            "question": "How does Mathematical finance relate to Statistical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8830597996711731,
            "question": "How does understanding Mathematical finance contribute to the field of Statistical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8244870901107788,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a concept used in both Statistical finance and Mathematical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7991479635238647,
            "question": "In what ways do Statistical finance and Mathematical finance overlap?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5931800007820129,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of Statistical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5251660943031311,
            "question": "Are there any specific areas within finance where Statistical finance is particularly relevant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48367318511009216,
            "question": "What are some key tools or techniques employed in Statistical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33378830552101135,
            "question": "What are some real-world applications of Statistical finance principles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3209385573863983,
            "question": "What are some potential challenges faced by practitioners in Statistical finance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23437601327896118,
            "question": "Can you explain the relationship between risk management and Statistical finance?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Statistical finance is about Mathematical finance.",
            "html": "dbpedia_117_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential challenges faced by practitioners in Statistical finance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_117_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some real-world applications of Statistical finance principles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_117_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key tools or techniques employed in Statistical finance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_117_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_117_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents repeatedly mention and define mathematical finance as a field of study that applies mathematical models and methods to analyze financial markets and securities, as well as to manage financial risk. This suggests that statistical finance is related to or perhaps a synonym for mathematical finance."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that mathematical finance involves advanced statistical methods and tools, which supports the statement that statistical finance is about mathematical finance. Therefore, the query \"Statistical finance is about Mathematical finance\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Response: {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}